<div id="welcomecontainer">
<div class="container">
    <div class="row clearfix">
        <div class="col-md-12 column">
            <div class="jumbotron">
                <h1>
                    Welcome To TrackerDash
                </h1>
                <h1><small> Lets get started. </small></h1>
                <h2>
                    To find out more about how to configure your TrackerDash server and get going <a href="https://github.com/wedgieedward/TrackerDash/wiki">click here.</a>
                </h2>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>
<div class="container">
    <div class="row clearfix">
        <div class="col-md-12 column">
            <div class="panel-group" id="panel-254778">
                <div class="panel panel-default">
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                         <a class="panel-title collapsed" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#panel-254778" href="#panel-element-623231">About TrackerDash</a>
                    </div>
                    <div id="panel-element-623231" class="panel-collapse collapse">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <p>
                                TrackerDash was created as a University Final Year Project inspired by problems faced day-to-day working in industry.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                There are many data analytics dashboards out there that had their own niches and selling points but there were common drawbacks to each of them, such as:
                                <ul>
                                    <li>No option to host locally.</li>
                                    <li>API limits.</li>
                                    <li>Targetted towards non API users.</li>
                                    <li>Not being able to retrieve historic graph data.</li>
                                    <li>Not being able to save graphs or retrieve graph data.</li>
                                    <li>$$$</li>
                                </ul>
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                With TrackerDash, the aim was to create an API driven data analytics server that can be hosted locally, <i>so you can store and display sensitive information</i>, that is lightweight and horizonally scalable.
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                Feedback will be greatly received and feel free to fork this project and expand on it's functionality.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="panel panel-default">
                    <div class="panel-heading">
                         <a class="panel-title collapsed" data-toggle="collapse" data-parent="#panel-254778" href="#panel-element-576134">Licensing Information</a>
                    </div>
                    <div id="panel-element-576134" class="panel-collapse collapse">
                        <div class="panel-body">
                            <p>
                                TrackerDash makes extensive use of <a href="http://www.highcharts.com/products/highcharts">Highcharts JS</a> which is licensed under creative commons. While under creative commons you are free to use TrackerDash and HighCharts software for non-commercial purposes, running this software might conflict with their Licensing terms, which can be found <a href="http://shop.highsoft.com/faq">here.</a>
                            </p>
                            <p>
                                TrackerDash and all it's code is Licensed under <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beerware">Beerware</a>, so feel free to do what ever you want with this code for non commercial purposes.
                            </p>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </div>
</div>
</div>
